Kheel, Theodore W. Additional Files. 6021/010
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- NYC Development + Economic Data, 1966-1979 (Box 23, Folder 41)
- NYC Development + Economic Data - Ehrenhalt Reports, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 42)
- NYC Development + Economic Data - Ehrenhalt Reports, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 43)
- NYC Governmental Process + Structure + Kheel Articles, 1952-1983 (Box 23, Folder 44)
- NYC Private Transit (Buses) Kheel as Impartial Arbitrator, 1949-1955 (Box 23, Folder 45)
- NYC Transit - Kheel as Impartial Arbitrator - amalgamated Queens, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 46)
- NYC Transit Authority + Transport Workers Union, 1954-1982 (Box 23, Folder 47)
- NYC Transit - Mayors Fact finding, 1948-1974 (Box 23, Folder 48)
- NYC Bus states, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  June 6 - July 20
- NYC Bus states, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  July 21 - Nov 29
- NYC Bus Strikes, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 51)
  May 25 - Dec 29
- NYC Bus Strikes, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  Nov
- NYC Bus Strikes, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  Dec
- NYC Bus Strikes, 1952-1953 (Box 23, Folder 54)
  Jan 1952 - Dec 1953
- NYC Bus Strikes, 1954-1960 (Box 23, Folder 55)
- NYC Subway + Bus Strikes, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- NYC Subway + Bus Strikes, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- NYC subway + Bus Strikes, 1963-1964 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- NYC Subway + Bus Strikes, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  July 27- Dec 24
- NYC Subway + Bus Strikes, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  Dec 25, 1965 - Jan 5, 1966
- NYC Subway + Bus Strikes, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  Jan 6-11
- NYC Subway + Bus Strikes, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  Jan 12-26
- NYC Subway + Bus Strike, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- NYC Subway + Bus Strikes, 1969-1971 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- NYC subway + Bus Strikes, 1973-1979 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- NYC Subway + Bus Strikes, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- NY Metropolitan transit Authority, 1969-1983 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- NY Magazine - Rupert Murdoch (Box 24, Folder 13)
- NY Post: Gail Sheehy Profile of Dorothy Sheff, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- New York Times - Excerpt from The Kingdom + the Power (Gay Talese) (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Newspaper Disputes + Strikes, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Newspaper disputes + Strikes, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  March 30 - June 27
- Newspaper Disputes + Strikes, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  June 30 - Sept 18
- Newspaper disputes + Strikes, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  Sept. 18-24
- Newspaper disputes + Strikes, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  Sept 25 - Oct 9
- Newspaper Disputes + Strikes, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  Oct 10-Nov 16
- Newspaper disputes + Strikes, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Newspaper disputes + Strikes, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  Mar 11- April 1
- Newspaper disputes + Strikes, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  April 1-30
- Newspaper disputes + Strikes, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  May 1-Nov6
- Newspaper disputes + Strikes, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- Newspaper disputes + Strikes, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  Mar 24 - April 20
- Newspaper Disputes + Strikes, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  April 21 - may 27
- Newspaper disputes + Strikes, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  June 27 - Nov 10
- Newspaper disputes + strikes, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 30)
- Newspaper disputes + Strikes, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 31)
- Newspaper disputes + Strike, 1975-1977 (Box 24, Folder 32)
- Newspaper Disputes + Strikes, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  Sept. 1-30
- Newspaper Dispute + Strikes, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  Oct 2-31
- Newspaper disputes + Strikes, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  Nov 6, 1978 - April 27, 1979
- Newspaper disputes + Strikes - NY Post, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 36)
- Newspaper Disputes + Strikes - My Daily News, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 37)
- Newspaper disputes + Strikes - NY Daily News, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  Aug 2 - Nov 20
- Newspaper disputes + Strikes - NY Daily News, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  Nov 20 - Dec. 24
- Newspaper Issues - Possible Safe of Daily News, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  Dec 20, 1981 - March 29, 1982
- Newspaper Issues - Possible Sale of Daily News, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  April 5 - May 25
- Newspaper Issues - Possible sale of NY Post, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 42)
- Newspaper Issues - Possible sale of Amsterdam News, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 43)
- NY Daily News Strike Kheel + Freeman Manuscript, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 44)
- NY Daily News Strike Chronology of Key Events, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 45)
- NY Daily News strike + Sale, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 46)
- Pennsylvania State University Controversy, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 47)
- Samuel R. Pierce Jr. (Box 24, Folder 48)
- Plumbing industry (Box 24, Folder 49)
- Police Disputes + Strikes (Box 24, Folder 50)
- Police Review Bd, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 51)
- Punta cana Beach Resort, 1974-1994 (Box 24, Folder 52)
- Queens College controversy, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 53)
- Railroad Dispute + Strikes, 1964-1967 (Box 24, Folder 54)
- Railroad disputes + Strikes, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 55)
- Railroad Disputes + Strikes, 1980-1983 (Box 24, Folder 56)
- Republic national Bank, 1964-1992 (Box 24, Folder 57)
- Sanitation Workers Disputes + Strikes, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 58)
- P.L. "Roy" Siemiller, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 59)
- Stirling Homex Corp., 1969-1978 (Box 24, Folder 60)
- Taxi Disputes + Strikes, 1965-1966 (Box 24, Folder 61)
- Teachers disputes + Strikes, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Teachers Disputes + Strikes, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Teachers disputes + Strikes, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Teachers Disputes + Strikes, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Teachers Disputes + Strikes - Oceanhill - Brownsville, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- teachers Disputes + Strikes, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- teachers Disputes + Strikes, 1970-1975 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- transit Fares, 1955-1963 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Transit Fares + Tolls, 1965-1968 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Transit Fares + Tolls, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Transit Fares + tolls, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Transit Fares + tolls, 1971-1973 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Transit Fares + tolls, 1974-1978 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Transport Workers Union, 1958-1984 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Transportation Bond Issue, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Transportation Bond Issue / Railroad Presentation bond, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- transportation Policy, 1955-1957 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Transportation Policy, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Transportation Policy, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Transportation Policy - Port of NY Authority, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Transportation Policy - Port of NY Authority, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Transportation Policy - Port NY Authority, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Transportation Policy - Port of NY Authority, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Transportation Policy - port of NY Authority covenant (1973 Rutgers - Law Review), 1962 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Transportation Policy - Port of NY Authority, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Transportation Policy - Port of NY Authority, 1974-1977 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- United Nations, 1979-1989 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- U.N. Rio conference - 1992 Earth Pledge, Earth Summit (Box 25, Folder 28)
- UN Conference - Vienna 1993 + Cairo, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Vietnam War - Paris Peace Talks, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Wage Stabilization - Nixon 1971 Program (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Wage Stabilization WWII (Box 25, Folder 32)
- Robert F. Wagner (on leaving office as mayor), 1963 (Box 25, Folder 33)
- War Labor Board, 1942-1946 (Box 25, Folder 34)
- Westside Convention Center, 1973-1980 (Box 25, Folder 35)
- West Side Highway (Westway), 1974-1988 (Box 25, Folder 36)
- Western Union - Ouster of Ch. + CEO Flanagan, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 37)
- world Trade Center, 1969-1975 (Box 25, Folder 38)
- Whitney M. Young, Jr., 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 39)
- TWK Scrapbook, 1997-2001 (Box 25, Folder 40)
- TWK Scrapbook, 1997-2001 (Box 25, Folder 41)
- TWK Scrapbook, 2002-2004 (Box 25, Folder 42)
- Easton Articles + newspaper Clippings folder 2 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Easton Hope (Koehler/Kheel Realty), 2005-2006 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Einstein, Joseph RE: Dr. Dave Follet, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- experiments in Art and Technology, Inc. Miscellaneous Newspaper clips, 1967-1968 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- experiments in Art and Technology, Inc. Operations and information Newsletter, Proceedings, 1968-1969 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- experiments in Arts and Technology, Inc. New York times, 1967-1970 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Experiments in Art and Technology, Inc. time, 1967-1968 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Experiments in Art and Technology, Inc. AFL-CIO News, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- experiments in Art and Technology, Inc. Spectrum Magazine, 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Experiments in Art and Technology, Inc. miscellaneous Articles + documents, 1957-1968 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- 3 Hanover Square - Mortgage and Consulting Fee Agreement, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Kheel Towers - Re: Fashion Place Associates Renovation Phase Requisition, 1975-1976 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Kheel Towers: Fashion Place Associates Renovation Phase Agreements, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Kheel Towers - Re: Fashion Place Associates Renovation Phase FHA Application, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Kheel Towers - Re: Fashion Place Associates Renovation Phase 3rd Amendment of Partnership, 1975-1976 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Kheel Towers Re: Fashion Place Associates Renovation Phase Phase III, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Fashion Place Associates Lease with Shapiro, Julius 6341.14.10.3 (Phantom Sales), 1971-1976 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Fashion Place Associates Lease with rizzuto, Thomas, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Fashion Place Associates Lease with Rettino, Anthony, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Fashion Place Correspondence, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Fashion Place Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Fashion Place Correspondence, 1984-1988 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Correspondence + Memos, 315 7th Ave. Assoc. Fashion Place, 1974-1980 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- Kheel Towers - Re: Fashion Place Associates Renovation Phase Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- Fashion Place Tax Information (IRS) (Folder 1), 1990-1994 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Fashion Place Tax Information (IRS) (Folder 2), 1978-1990 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Financial Statements Fashion Place Associates, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- 315 7th Ave Condominium, 1990-1992 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- 315 7th Ave Condominium, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- 315 7th Ave condos (Tax Return), 1992 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Fashion Place - conversion Plan Miscellaneous, 1975-1988 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Fashion Place Associates Legal research RE: Conversion Plan, Notes, etc., 1985-1990 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Fashion Place Associates: Condominium Offering Plan "Red Herring", 1988-1991 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Deed Fashion Place, 1975-1986 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Fashion Place/ HPD Litigation Documents, 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  Dec 97- April 98
- Dec 97 - April 98, 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- folder 3, 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Folder 4, 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Nov 98 - Dec 00, 1998-2000 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Folder 2, 1998-2000 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Folder 3, 1998-2000 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Folder 1 April 01 - august 02, 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- folder 2, 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Depositions, 1999-2000 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1990-2002 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  March 1990 - Aug. 2002
- Extras March 90 - April 02, 1990-2002 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Schedule of Apartments, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Legal Research (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Notes, 1998-1999 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Insurance, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Drafts March 90 - April 98, 1990-1998 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Fashion Place v. HPD - Drafts + Pleadings Draft Affidavit of TW Kheel, 1991-1998 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Fashion Place Fashion Place Associtates v. NYC Dept. of housing v. NYC Dept. of housing, Preservation + Development Pleadings, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Fashion Place Associates v. HPD - Drafts/Proceedings Draft Petition, 1991-1994 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Fashion Place RE: HPD Legal Research, 1977-1990 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Fashion Place v. HPD/ A/G's Office Extra copies of correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Legal Research (cozier), 1998 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Fashion Place v. HPD Assurance of Discontinuance, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Fashion Place: state of New York v. Fashion Place, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Complaints and answers filed with DHCR, 1990-1992 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- State of NY v. Fashion Place Apro. Fashion Place, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Fashion Place Associates Financial Inf - Mortgage Schedule/Lease Categories, 1985-1992 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Market Lease analysis, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- F.I.T. v. Fashion Place Associates (Schwartz Laudes Assocs v. NYC Conciliation + Appeals Board), 1984-1989 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- State of New York v. Fashion Place Associates et al. Extras Copies of pleadings, Drafts, etc., 1991 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Fashion Place: Exchange of correspondence RE: Dept. of housing, Preservation, + Development (Folder 1), 1988-1992 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Fashion Place: Exchange of Correspondence RE: Dept. of housing, Preservation, + Development, 1990-1994 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Fashion Place Re: Tenants correspondence, 1991-1994 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Fashion Place: Exchange of Correspondence w/ the Attorney General's Office, 1990-1993 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Fashion Place, RE: HPD, Correspondence Letter to City Collector, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  July 12
- Fashion Place, Re: HPD, correspondence notices Sent to Tenants, 1990-1991 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- fashion Place, Re: HPD, Correspondence Rent Computation Forms, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Fashion Place, RE: HPD, Correspondence Breakdown of Lease Categories, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- fashion Place, Re: HPD, Correspondence Stabilized Leases, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Fashion Place, RE: HPD, Correspondence Tenant Payment Report, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Fashion Place, Re: HPD, Correspondence 1991 DHCR Rent Registration Forms (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Fashion Place: Complaints + Answers Filled Out w/ DHCR (Barnes/Nash/Luv), 1991-1992 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- F.I.T. v. Fashion Place (second Action) Leases, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- State of New York v. Fashion Place et al. Articles, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Fashion Place Associates v. Eiselle, Luu, + Barnes/Nash Non Payment Dwelling Petitions, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- F.I.T. v. Fashion Place Extra copies of Pleadings, 1987-1995 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- F.I.T. v. Fashion Place Leases Submitted to Plaintiff on TWK Deposition, 1980-1985 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- F.I.T. v. Fashion Place Deposition of Theodore W. Kheel, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- Fashion Place Litigation Binder Folder 1, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Fashion Place Litigation Binder Folder 2, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Fashion Place Litigation Binder Folder 3 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- March 90 - Dec 92, 1990-1992 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Nov 92 - Nov 96 folder 1 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Nov 92 - Nov 96 folder 2 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Nov 92 - Nov 96 folder 3, 1992-1996 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Nov 92 - Nov 96 cont. folder 4, 1992-1996 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Nov 92 - Nov 96 folder 5, 1992-1996 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- F.I.T. v. Fashion Place clients documents, 1976-1987 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- F.I.T. Student Housing Corp. and Claire Ehrlich v. Fashion Place, 1989-1995 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- F.I.T. v. Fashion Place - Folder 1 Pleadings, 1990-1995 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- F.I.T. Student housing (Folder 2) v. Fashion Place Pleadings, 1996-1997 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- F.I.T. v. Fashion Place Associates Pleadings folder 1, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- F.I.T. v. Fashion Place Associates Pleadings Folder 2, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- F.I.T. v. Fashion Place Associates Lease Agreements, 1978-1989 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- F.I.T. v. Fashion Place Associates Sublease Agreements, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Fashion Place: F.I.T. v. Fashion Place Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- F.I.T. v. Fashion Place Associates Certificate of incorporation, etc. of F.I.T. Dormitory corp., 1960-1987 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- F.I.T. v. Fashion Place Associates Merger of FIT Student Housing corp. into FIT Dormitory corp., 1987 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- FIT v Fashion Place Associates Notes, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- FIT v. Fashion Place Associates RE: Rent due Fashion Place, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Fashion Place - FIT v. Fashion Place Assoc. Info re Tax Exemption + Rent Regulation, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- FIT v Fashion Place Assoc. Tenant Lists/Rent Rail, 1983-1988 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- FIT v Fashion Place Associates checks, 1981-1987 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- FIT v. Fashion Place Associates Kheel Tower Resident Handbook (Box 31, Folder 17)
- FIT v. Fashion Place Associates Legal Research, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Notes, 315 7th Ave. Assoc., 1976 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Appraisals, 315 7th Ave Associates, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Booklets + Leaflets, 315 7th Ave. Assoc., 1976 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Fashion Place Partnership Agreements Folder 1, 1988-1993 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Fashion Place Partnership Agreements Folder 2, 1987-1988 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Mortgage 315 7th Ave Assoc., 1974-1975 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous 315 7th Ave Assoc., 1975-1977 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Litho Documents 315 7th Ave - Partnership, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- fashion Place Karate Institute Settlement Agreement, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Karate Institute, Inc. 315 7th Avenue Associates, 1972-1975 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Fashion Place Associates Hold Over Proceeding vs. Karate Institute, 1972-1977 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- fashion Place: Karate: strict Foreclosure (Aborted), 1975 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Certiorari Proceeding, Fashion Place Associates RE: 315 7th Ave Assoc., 1975 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- HAD - Preliminary certificate of Partial Tax Exemption Kheel tower, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Source of Funds + Disbursements Partnership - Kheel Tower, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Partnership Returns 315 7th Ave Assoc Partner, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Muriel Kirsch v. Fashion Place Associates 315 7th Ave Associates, 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Raynes - Shaun Casey Dispute 315 7th Ave Assoc., 1979 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Matter of Conversion to Condominium 315 7th Ave. Assoc. Partnership, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 19)
- 1982 Purchase of Mortgage 315 7th Ave Assoc (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Drafts; Part, Agreement + Certificates 315 7th Ave assoc., 1975 (Box 32, Folder 21)
- Finals; Part, Agreement + certificates 315 7th Ave Assoc., 1975-1983 (Box 32, Folder 22)
- Fashion Place Assoc. - FPA Partnership Agreement, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  folder 1
- Fashion Place Assoc. - FPA Partnership Agreement, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  folder 2
- Fashion Place Assoc.Amended, restated Partnerships Agreement Tabs 1-37, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Fashion Place Associates - Binder, Amended + Restated Partnership Agreement Tabs 1-50, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Fashion Place Assoc. - Binder, Amended + Restated Partnership Agreement Tabs 51-100, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Fashion Place Assoc. - Binder, Amended + Restated Partnership Agreement (Folder 2) Tabs 101-200, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Fashion Place Assoc. - Binder, FPA Tabs 1-90 folder 1, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Fashion Place Associates - binder, FPA Tabs 1-89, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Fashion Place Associates - Binder FPA Tabs 90 - 200 folder 1, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Fashion Place Associates - Binder FPA Tabs 90-200 Folder 2, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Fashion Place - Appraisal of Apartments (Jerome Haimes Realty), 2000 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Fashion Place: Transfer of Apt. to Jenna Smith, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Fashion Place Associates Lee Berkovits v. Tarko, Smith, FPA, Belkin Burden, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Fashion Place Assignment of Interest to Ann S. Kheel, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Fashion Place Associates Documents (Partnership Transfers), 1992-1993 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Fashion Place Associates Distribution of apts. To Partners, 1996-1997 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- FPA: copies of documents RE: FPA Trust Agreements, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Fashion Place Extra copies of FPA documents, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Martin Raynes RE: Fashion Place Associates, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Fashion Place Assoc. - Mortgage Loan, First Natl. City Bank, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Tomken Management Limited RE: Fashion Place Associates, 1981-1984 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- 315 7th Ave Seafre, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Fashion Place: Election of Managers, 1999-2001 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- FPA - Broker Dealer Statement Filing Fee, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Loan Fashion Place Bank of NY, 1989-1993 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Fashion Place Associates - Partnership Account Agreement Bank of New York, 1987-1994 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Fashion Place Miscellaneous, 1999-2001 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Fashion Place Associates (General correspondence) RIP (Ralph J Palmer), 1973-1975 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Federation of international civil Servants - Associations, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- Follet, Dr. David A. Re: Lenox hill hospital, 1995-1997 (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Forum Future PRS, Inc. corporate Records (Binder), 1994 (Box 34, Folder 21)
- Equal Employment opportunity Commission v. Union Trust - Leslie Fourton, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 22)
- NationsBank Freeman, Brian - correspondence (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Nations Bank Freeman, Brian - Material on Pension funds, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 24)
- Nations Bank Freeman, Brian - ASB Capital management, Letter of Intent, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 25)
- Nations Bank Freeman, Brian - Management contract, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 26)
- Nations Bank Freeman, Brian - resume of Jane Kheel, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 27)
- Nations Bank Freeman, Brian - Calabrese Resume, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 28)
- Nations Bank CV - Brian M Freeman, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 29)
- Nations Bank Asset Management Foundation for Workers, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 30)
- Freeman, Brian Golden Screens Interactive Technologies, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 31)
- Freeman, Brian - The Reindustrialization Fund (Nations Bank) Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 34, Folder 32)
- Freeman, Brian - The Reindustrialization Fund Drafts, 1994-1996 (Box 34, Folder 33)
- Freeman, Brian - The Reindustrialization Fund AFL-CIO Union Membership and Info, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 34)
- Freeman, Brian - The Reindustrialization Fund Freeman, Brian v. TWU, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 35)
- Fusion Telecom International (Turits) Promissory Note, 1998-1999 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Fusion Telecom International (Turits) Warrant to Purchase Stock, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Fusion Telecom International (Turits) Term Sheet, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Fusion Telecom International (Turits) Subscription Agreement, 1998-1999 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Fusion Telecom International (Turits) Questionnaires, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Fusion Telecom International (Turits) Private Placement Memorandum, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Fusion Telecom International (Turits) Private Placement Memorandum, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- The Gordon Restaurant Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Reiner v. Raoul Garino, Inc. (Garden Restaurant - Lambrou), 1985 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Pari Passu, The Garden Restaurant - White v. Bernard Roy, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- The Garden Restaurant - Assumed Name Certificate, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- The Garden Restaurant RE: Con. Ed., 1986 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- The Garden Restaurant RE: Harlem Paper Products, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Agreement between Lambrou + Vitelas + Kheel Garden Restaurant, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Gateway Sporting Goods Co. Correspondence and Memos, 1973-1985 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- Gateway sporting Goods Co. Miscellaneous, 1974-1977 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Gateway Sporting Goods Co. Form 3, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Gateway Sporting Goods Co. Form 10-Q, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Gateway Sporting Goods Co. Questionnaires (Form 10k), 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 19)
- Gateway sporting Goods Co. Form 10K Questionnaires, 1977-1980 (Box 35, Folder 20)
- Gateway Sporting Goods Co. Minutes, 1974-1978 (Box 35, Folder 21)
- Gateway Sporting Goods Co. (1978) Stock Option Plan, 1978-1979 (Box 35, Folder 22)